<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Engels on GIP 2015-2016 Yordi Coussement</title>
    <link>http://yordicimmalle.github.io/GIP/engels/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Engels on GIP 2015-2016 Yordi Coussement</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 14:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://yordicimmalle.github.io/GIP/engels/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>The influences of IT</title>
      <link>http://yordicimmalle.github.io/GIP/engels/autobiography/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2015 18:35:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yordicimmalle.github.io/GIP/engels/autobiography/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My name is Yordi Coussement and I’m 18 years old. I’m studying IT at school which is Immaculata Institute Oostmalle. In my time off I’m always behind my computer. Sometimes just for fun and some social networking, but nearly anytime I make some music. I like making music because it’s my passion. As you can read I’m not a person who likes to game for hours and hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My first touch with a computer was when I was 6 or 7 years old I think. We had just bought a new computer and I used it for playing Pinball and for listening to music. First I thought… “Wow this is a cool device” but after a few months it became way cooler because I discovered the Internet. It was something I think I had never heard about but if so I probably couldn’t remember it anymore so it was like a new world. I was browsing through it and I found the first game sites. I always played “Bubble Shooter” or a race game. Damn what a nice period that was! It didn’t take long to find out how messenger (MSN) worked. I added some friend from school and yes you know what’s coming now… I was chatting for hours and hours with my friends. It was something cool because we could talk with each other without a phone. I have to admit… it was a great time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IT means a lot to me. I use it every day and I think that if it disappears, I will get a depression. I spend 2 to 3 hours on my computer a day and more than 5 hours a day in vacations and at weekends. Sometimes I like to work at some websites myself, but when I’m behind my computer I’m probably working with music. It is something I really like. There are some days that I’m producing music for 7 or 8 hours. Sometimes I also work at night because that’s a moment when I have a lot of inspiration.
It is something very unique because there aren’t many people who can say they know something about the software. I have been doing it for 2 years now and believe me… I always learn some new things about music production.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My ambitions with IT are that I will have a job with a big company where I manage the network. I also want to have my own little company which offers a webhost or other server-based things. Of course I will also keep producing music so I think I will need IT for several years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After all you can say that IT has become an important part in my life. I use it for several hours every day so I can’t imagine a life without it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://scontent-fra3-1.xx.fbcdn.net/hphotos-xlp1/v/t1.0-9/20023_842267222515033_2892206337495177343_n.jpg?oh=fcd88bca5969f178f79ff48c38eb113e&amp;amp;oe=56FAF9EF&#34; alt=&#34;alt text&#34; /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IT-Tapa Instruction video: The English Way</title>
      <link>http://yordicimmalle.github.io/GIP/engels/movie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2015 18:53:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yordicimmalle.github.io/GIP/engels/movie/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;tutorial-part-1:44684454d38aa08e0c5bdd879390002b&#34;&gt;Tutorial Part 1:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/3WsNn7D7XLE&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;tutorial-part-2:44684454d38aa08e0c5bdd879390002b&#34;&gt;Tutorial Part 2:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Vd68ZdNM0x0&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review about ClickShare</title>
      <link>http://yordicimmalle.github.io/GIP/engels/review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 14:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yordicimmalle.github.io/GIP/engels/review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am going to talk about Clickshare. Clickshare is a tool used for interactive presentations during meetings. It is possible to share the screen of your pc to a large tv screen or beamer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my training company they use it in their meeting rooms. In every room there is a big flatscreen and 2 to 4 Clickshare dongles. During meetings they use the tool so the participants of the meeting are able to see what the leader is doing on his computer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the internet there aren’t a lot reviews about Clickshare, but I think the reviews I found were very good and told the truth about the tool. The evaluation of the tool was very positive. They said Clickshare was easy to use and that it makes any collaborative process infinitely more engaging. The best thing about it is that it is innovative and currently unique. In my opinion this isn’t completely true, but I’ll come back to this point later in this review.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The negative things I read about Clickshare were the high price to buy the installation, the reset problems and the smartphone software. As you can read, Clickshare is a very expensive tool. To buy a full installation with 4 dongles, you have to count on 4,000 to 5,000 euros. Another negative point is the reset problem. There is a little problem with the wireless receiver so that you have to reset the device and wait 5 to 10 minutes before you can use it again. This is a bit of a shame because of the high price. Let us hope it will be solved with a fresh update in the future. The last negative point was the mobile app. There is a mobile app of Clickshare, but it isn’t possible to share the entire screen of the device. You have to make screenshots and upload them to the app before you can share what you want.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now what is my opinion about it? I really like the ‘press and play’ feature. You just have to connect the dongle with your PC, run the software and press the button on the dongle. It saves a lot of time during an important meeting which is in my opinion very positive because you know the expression: ‘Time is money!’. As I told before, the point of an innovative and currently unique thing isn’t completely true. There are some other options to share your screen to another screen. Think about Apple TV, Samsung Smart Link and the new Chromecast systems. They are much cheaper and better I think. The best thing about the tool is that it eliminates cables. The only thing you need is the dongle with a 10cm usb-cable. Also the feature to collaborate from multiple devices is very awesome and handy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I do not like about Clickshare is that you have to reset the wireless receiver almost every time you use it. Also the price isn’t very good. You have to pay a lot of money for it and it doesn’t always work without issues.
The worst thing about it is the smartphone app. It would be nice and handy if it was possible to share the entire screen of your smartphone to a larger screen, but unfortunately it isn’t possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conclusion… Clickshare is a must have in every medium-sized and large company. It saves a lot of time during your meetings, it eliminates cables and it is possible to collaborate with multiple devices.
The advice I give is: ‘Think before you buy’. Why? There are some flaws and it is very expensive. Maybe you can try to use Chromecast before you buy Clickshare. It can save you over more than 4,000 euros.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>